Hey everyone, welcome to this video. It's a different one than usual because normally I am wearing the designs I want to show you, but this time I'm showing them to you on a screen because I don't have these designs here.
But I think they're awesome. I want to introduce you to a bunch of alternative fashion designers from all over the world. I hope you can find some inspiration or find some new designers. Yeah, I love them. Let's go.
First off is Altoranova. They have studios in Chicago and in Cannes, France and they
produce and design every piece in-house. What I love about them is they work with materials
like silicone and acrylic and they make breastplates, bikinis, swimwear, bodysuits. They are really
innovative in what they're doing. So they took silicone and made it fashion. Some superstars
are wearing their designs. It's on the runway, it looks so high quality and the colors are so
outstanding with the ultraviolet colors, the chrome colors. Maybe you saw them on social media a few
years ago. Some of their clips went viral and that's I think what gave them a huge leap in
publicity. I know that their pieces are a bit pricey so I don't know if you want to spend money
but if you do at least you have a designer piece.
Continuing with bizarre design NL from the Netherlands, Jeroen van der Klees and he's actually a technical engineer
but his specialty is corsets and
restrictive fashion so to say like wobble skirts and
arm binders, so I've
talked to him, we wrote a few messages, he's really really nice. Unfortunately I did not have the
chance yet to work with him but maybe in the future. His pieces are basically structural art
pieces so you see that there is a technical background behind the conception and construction
of the corsets for example. You can lace them down really really tight and for that it needs
great craftsmanship. It's also it doesn't look too kinky but the designs are really kinky
from like a restrictive point of view but on the other hand they're still fashionable so they do
look like something special if you want to order something from him you can have a look at his
price list on the web page but just get in touch with him personally I think that's the easiest way
next is Gia she's located in Milan Italy originally she's from Bulgaria she's a trained
fashion designer and she does a lot of high couture leather works and you can order it via
her catalog on her web page I just love her designs she's her own model and obviously her
muse and the pictures she takes are incredible and she also looks incredible and I love her
designs they're clear they are powerful they're bold like combining the leather with these huge
spikes is always something I adore also when she's wearing masks and face pieces she does out of
leather it doesn't look tacky it doesn't look um yeah too fetishy it just looks so futuristic and
unique and I think it's really fashion and not just I don't know for the leather lovers but for
everyone and also the bag with the huge spikes at at the bottom is something I don't know no one
has thought of before and it looks just so great
up next is Cecilio Designs from Spain he does specialize in leather crafting and he does a lot
of masks that's how I got to know him and by now also of course that I've seen he made shoes
recently which I love and a really well-known alternative fashion designer
been around for years already. I think the designs are fantastic. They're kind
of organic looking so like a living thing but also like art and like
structures. You just have a look for yourself because it's hard to describe
and it's top-notch quality. There is an online shop in which you can see some of
the pieces but you have to write them a message to order. The rule for this video
that I did not wear something from the designers I'm introducing is not true in
this case because a few years ago at the Boutique Bizarre in Hamburg I tried on a
mask from him like just a high upper face mask it was so great it felt so good
like the leather was really soft but also firm I think the designs are great
Now I'm going to show you Corset Factory Products.
They're from Istanbul, Turkey and they do everything by hand.
They specialize in heavy PVC wear.
They make a lot of hoods and collars, also restrictive design.
If you want to order there, write him because he does everything made to order.
He's also a very nice person.
I wrote a few messages with him. Unfortunately, I did not have the chance to work with him yet.
If you are more on the kinky side, you should definitely have a look.
What I love about his social media presence is that there are a lot of making of videos.
So you can have a peek over his shoulder and see how he makes the products, which is great.
I love to watch them.
Does someone of you own something from one of the designers I just told you about?
Please write it in the comments and how did you like this video and this kind of
like I'm not showing it but I'm going to show you pictures structure. Also leave
leave a thumbs up also but leave a comment in the comment section down
below. Yeah it was something new I hope you liked it I hope you enjoyed it and
check out the Instagram pages of the designers for more pictures check out
their web pages and check out my channel for more from me. I will see you around in another video
here. Have a nice day. Bye.